

# Magdalena Mishkov



**UX/UI** Designer

https://mishkovm.github.io/portfolio/

### **About**

I am a designer with experience in **UX/UI**, **graphic**, and **web** design. The seven years in the banking field provided me with solid **analytical** and **organisational** skills, as well as ability to understand people and find the best solution for their problems. Today I use those key skills to create **inclusive digital solutions** through research and empathy. I aspire to WOW users with a "**how didn't they come up with this before?**" type of impression.

### **Education**

UX Gym Training, Bonanza Studios, 01/2024 - present

UX/UI Design Certification, Brainster, 06/2021 - 06/2022

Master of Science (MSc), Monetary economics, finances and banking,

Faculty of Economics, University Ss. Cyril and Methodius, 10/2013 - 09/2018

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Financial Management,

Faculty of Economics, University Ss. Cyril and Methodius, 10/2009 - 10/2013

### Work experience

Designer, Homebase Real Estate GmbH, Berlin, 06/2024 - present

- creating strong brand identity to our clients
- preparing online and offline set of creatives
- building landing pages from scratch to final hand-off
- strategic planning and designing visual appealing creatives for Social media campaigns

Self-employed UI/UX Designer, 03/2024 - present

providing design and development services to a broad range of freelance clients

Junior Designer, allmyhomes GmbH, Berlin, 04/2023 - 10/2023

- creating and implementing user-centered interfaces through data-driven analysis; building responsive landing pages from concept to final hand-off
- improving the user experience by continuous testing
- strategic planning and designing visual appealing creatives for Social media campaigns
- collaborating with Branding, Performance marketing and Project managers to ensure deliverables are aligned with the client's vision cross-functional collaboration

Design Intern, allmyhomes GmbH, Berlin, 10/2022 - 03/2023

supported graphic designers in their projects, which involved collecting **research**, creating advertisements material and **brainstorming alternative ideas** and realising them

Business Assistant of the MB, NLB Banka AD Skopje, Skopje, 07/2015 - 06/2019

provided comprehensive support to MB members, efficiently coordinating their daily activities, and facilitating smooth operations to enhance productivity and maximise their effectiveness

Bank Advisor, NLB Banka AD Skopje, Skopje, 01/2012 - 06/2015

successfully **identified customer needs** for both investment and lending, providing tailored financial solutions and advice that resulted in **increased customer engagement** and loyalty

Paderborn, Germany+491781861567magdalena.mishkov@gmail.com

## **Design skills**

Competitive Analysis
User Research
User Persona
User Journey
Empathy Maps
User Flow
Information Architecture
Typography & Layout
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Visual Design Principles
User Interface Design

#### Soft skills

Creative thinking
Empathy
Problem-solving
Quick learning
Collaboration
Adaptability
Time management
Curiosity
Can-do attitude

#### **Toolkit**

Figma
Adobe Creative Suite
(Photoshop, Illustrator,
InDesign)
Miro
Unbounce
Wordpress
Visual Studio
GitHub

## Languages

Macedonian - Native English - Business German - Intermediate French - Elementary